What are you talking about?
What do you mean by his cousin?
Who is his cousin?
I am sorry for being late...
Jun Seo.
(Episode 6)
Sin Ae, you look great.
Why are you crying?
It must've been hard for you.
No.
I don't believe that.
I heard you were doing great at school.
Jun Seo was proud of you.
There's nothing to brag about.
You were great, too.
You were the class president.
Didn't you go to college?
No.
What do you do, then?
- I work at a hotel.
- Do you?
Do you work at Tae Seok's hotel?
I start to work there as a manager
from next week.
What's your position?
I am in the Housekeeping Department.
I see.
Are you working full-time?
No, I'm not.
Did you come from the U.S. today?
No. I arrived yesterday.
Dad and Mom will come in a few days...
How are they?
Do you think they remember me?
I don't know.
Anyway, it is good to see you.
I have thought of you a lot.
Mom and Dad didn't want us
to talk about you.
We left for the U.S to forget everything.
We had tried to forget everything.
But I think that was too much.
How could we stop contacting
each other just like that?
I feel so bad for Eun Seo.
I feel terrible.
How could she live like that?
I can't imagine
how much she missed her parents.
If I were her...
How could you leave her like that?
How could you be so cruel?
Yoon Jun Seo, what did you do?
Where have you been until now?
Tae Seok.
You are right.
I didn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything.
Eun Seo, stay for the night.
I am going to bed. See you all tomorrow.
I should go now.
How can you go now?
I need to go to work
for something tomorrow.
I almost forgot.
Is that so? Then, let's go.
Jun Seo, what about Sin Ae?
No, Jun Seo.
Can you take me home?
Yes.
Can you go now?
Let's go.
I will take you home.
Sin Ae...
wants to see you.
I don't feel bad for you.
I don't.
Do I look pitiful?
No, you don't.
You are not pitiful.
Because...
I have your back from now on.
What are you going to do?
Calm down.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Jun Seo, don't say anything to Mom.
Don't tell her you found Eun Seo.
Sin Ae.
Mom is finally getting better
in the past few years.
She got sick because of Eun Seo.
Because she missed Eun Seo.
Do you really have to say that?
I'm sorry,
but I want Eun Seo to meet her mom.
I think that's the only thing
I can do for her.
You still don't care about me,
not even a little.
Now that you've found Eun Seo,
do you have no use for me now?
Yoon Sin Ae.
Yes, I'm Yoon Sin Ae.
I'm your sister, Yoon Sin Ae.
I was lonely in the U.S.
Mom was sick because she missed Eun Seo.
You and Dad kept your distance from me.
It was hard for me.
Seeing how Eun Seo is here now,
what will happen to me?
I didn't want to meet Eun Seo ever again.
All right.
Let's think about it.
Let's wait until Mom and Dad get here.
Hello.
Jun Seo? Where are you?
I'm at school.
I came here straight after
taking Yu Mi to the airport.
You didn't go to work, did you?
When do you finish work today?
Didn't you say you would leave early?
Professor, you have a visitor.
How can I help you?
You were pretty strong.
- It hurt for a few days.
- What do you want?
- Eun Seo.
- Did you meet Eun Seo?
No.
I guess she is doing well.
She has an amazing guardian here.
My mom is sick, so...
I'm not asking you a lot.
If you came here for that, excuse me now.
Professor.
If people find out you live with a girl,
what would your school do?
Do you think Eun Seo can keep her job?
Thanks,
I hope you can help me from time to time.
By the way, aren't we like brothers
from the same hometown?
You are bad.
You are so bad.
Why do you make me so miserable?
Is it not enough to bother me?
Why are you bothering my brother as well?
- I should go.
- Eun Seo.
- I'm fine.
- Why are you doing this to me?
I'm all right, Eun Seo.
Tae Seok.
Sin Ae.
Do you still love clinging like this?
- Have you started to work?
- No.
I start next week.
I came to introduce myself today.
Tae Seok, buy me lunch.
What do you mean?
I won't have lunch with you anymore.
Why? Do you have a new girl?
How did you know that?
Who is she?
How long will you keep her this time?
I'm not fooling around.
I met the CEO before coming here.
So you met my dad?
He told me to quit my job,
and get married.
You.
You should give up.
I'm not going out with girls anymore.
It is tasty.
Enjoy the meal,
since it's the last lunch with me.
Why are you so late?
It's a cleaning day.
Was it?
We'll do it now.
Do you know what my students told me?
They believed I was a student, but I lied.
Do I look that young?
What do you think? Do I look really young?
No, you look old.
You look very old.
What?
By the way, you looked scary earlier.
Of course,
you have no idea how strong I am.
I'm sorry.
If I had known you would be like that,
I wouldn't have given it.
It's all right.
Are you happy to meet me, Jun Seo?
What did you say? Who?
Don't you remember Yoon Jun Seo?
Eun Seo's brother.
Do you mean the family...
came back from the U.S.?
What's wrong?
Sin Ae.
This is a great workout.
It's not that easy.
Let's race to the main building.
So you want to race with your skills?
Have you got a lot of money?
Let's race.
If you win, you buy me breakfast.
If I win, you give me a kiss.
- What?
- Start!
It will take time
to get familiar with everything.
I am looking forward to working with you.
It went up, so...
It lasts longer this time.
You should give up.
I'm not going out with girls anymore.
I didn't have much time to know everything
since I was transferred on short notice.
So, I will need your support.
We will not have a lot of changes.
Please do what you have to do
in your position.
I am counting on all of you.
Is she really Sin Ae?
Sin Ae.
Lee Kang Hee, it has been a long time.
Yes, it has.
Sin Ae, it is good to see you.
I knew you would be in our department.
Are you glad to see me?
I asked Tae Seok for this.
I see.
By the way, why do people say
Manager Kim was fired because of you?
Did you ask Jun Seo
to make Tae Seok do something?
What are you talking about?
Anyway, people see things and talk.
So it wouldn't be any good
to show you know me.
Let's get to work now.
See you later.
Sin Ae.
Mom.
Are you Sin Ae?
Are you really Sin Ae?
Sin Ae.
- Sin Ae.
- Mom.
- Sin Ae...
It's great.
They, at least...
kept their word.
They kept their promise
to take good care of her.
Isn't she pretty?
Isn't she so pretty?
Yes, she is.
So, is she good at school?
Yes.
What should I do?
What do I have to do?
I didn't keep my word.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm sorry I have raised you like this.
So what should I do?
I should've never switched you.
I should've not.
I only made you live like this.
So, what can I do?
I am so sorry, Eun Seo. What should I do?
Sin Ae.
It is Eun Seo, isn't it?
What is it?
I'm just drawing it.
You're just drawing it?
You don't see her as your sister, do you?
You like her, but not as your sister,
do you?
Sin Ae.
Has she been sick?
Has she been very sick?
She didn't recognize Jun Seo and me
for a while.
She acted like she lived with you
in her dreams.
Because of me...
I'm not saying it's because of you.
But, if you stay with Jun Seo,
Mom will see you again.
I'm scared that she will get sick again.
Jun Seo probably feels sorry for Yu Mi.
You and Jun Seo
are not biologically related.
Yu Mi doesn't seem to know that.
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't do this to you.
But none of us were ourselves.
Finally, we settled down somehow.
Eun Seo, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid my family might become
as it was before.
I will not let that happen.
What do you mean?
Will everyone be fine if I leave?
Will everything be fine if I leave?
This is what you like, isn't it?
This is good, too.
What is this all about?
When did you do it all?
Did you finish work early today?
I cooked everything you like.
I'm a good girl, aren't I?
Thanks for the meal.
What? Haven't you seen me eating before?
I have, but I haven't seen you that often.
So I want to remember this.
You will see me eating
until you get sick of it.
All right.
I will get you some water.
Do you remember it?
You can have this now.
Okay, my treat.
I had it for a long time.
From now on, you can take care of this.
Do not break it.
If you do, they can't be together.
Do you want more soup?
Eun Seo.
Where are you going?
Jun Seo.
Let's go in.
Yoon Eun Seo.
I'm not Yoon Eun Seo.
Jun Seo, I'm Choi Eun Seo now.
I'm not that Eun Seo anymore, Jun Seo.
I thought I'd be happy if I met you again.
So, I worked hard until I met you.
I did my best not to disappoint you
when I met you.
That made me happy.
I was proud of myself.
Now I met you, but I'm not happy at all.
What is wrong with me?
Why am I getting miserable?
It would have been better
if we had never met.
Eun Seo, no.
No, Eun Seo. Stop it.
Let's go in.
I'll go. Let me go.
Let's forget that we have met.
Then I suppose we can all be happy.
Please forget we ever met.
No, Eun Seo.
No, I can't.
Don't leave.
Don't leave, Eun Seo.
I won't let you leave.
I don't care if you're not my sister.
Please stay with me.
Stay with me, Eun Seo.
Don't leave me, Eun Seo.
I won't let you leave.
Do you want to go to the beach?
You got almost everything. Thanks.
You come here very often, don't you?
If you come this often,
you should get married already.
Jun Seo wanted to talk with me.
About the wedding?
I don't think he wants to marry me.
He doesn't really talk about our wedding.
Doesn't he?
Then marry me.
Can I tell Eun Seo what you just said?
No way.
I don't understand.
Why are all the girls falling for you,
Tae Seok?
I think...
I treat them very well.
I fired the manager
who bullied Eun Seo the other day.
What did you do?
What is wrong with you?
Eun Seo would be very embarrassed.
Why would she be?
Her colleagues would bully
Eun Seo for that.
Would they?
Look around later
and come to have a coffee.
Okay.
Will you paint again?
Didn't you stop drawing
after you graduated?
It's a secret.
I see. You are going to draw someone.
Is it Eun Seo?
Yes. How do you know?
It's interesting.
Men who paint...
want to draw the girl
they fall in love with.
Is that so?
I've never painted a girl.
They probably meant nothing to you.
I think you really like Eun Seo.
Why is this clanking so much?
Is there something wrong with it?
Do you see that in me?
I see that.
Has Jun Seo painted you a lot?
Hasn't he painted you?
He has never painted me.
He said I was too beautiful to draw.
That's nonsense.
Jun Seo...
It's all right. I am okay with that.
I knew that.
I think it would be a meaningful life
if we...
respect and stay considerate
of each other.
You are so generous.
I actually live reminding myself that...
it is a meaningful way to live.
But, when I forget that sometimes,
it hurts a great deal.
Jun Seo.
Where is he?
I need to talk to you.
Can I come during the weekend?
No, I'll come.
I also have things to bring to Tae Seok.
Did you meet Tae Seok?
Were you surprised I asked you
to come here suddenly?
I need to talk to you, Yu Mi.
I need to talk to you, too.
Jun Seo, let's get married.
Marry me.
I'm tired of coming back and forth
from Seoul to Sokcho like this.
Let's get married.
Yu Mi.
I was actually upset with you.
You haven't discussed about me
moving to Sokcho.
You didn't consult with me
about living with Eun Seo here.
Also, you lied to me
that Eun Seo is your cousin.
Eun Seo...
We were supposed
to get married, weren't we?
Jun Seo, look at me.
Look at me.
Don't you love me?
I thought I could try.
I thought I should tell you this.
Because I care about you.
I think I should be honest with you.
No.
I should go.
I don't want to hear it.
I won't hear you.
I won't hear what you say.
Yu Mi.
I will not let you go, Jun Seo.
I will call you.
Have you seen the manager
who came with Sin Ae?
No, I haven't.
But I heard he was good-looking.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking about something now.
I wish I could sleep forever.
So I can see him in my dreams every day.
Are you doing that again?
At least I'm doing something.
What about you, then?
What about me?
I wish you had someone like Jun Seo.
How come Jun Seo is your brother?
No, he is not.
To be honest,
he and you are not related biologically.
No, you two are still siblings.
What can I do for you?
What can I do for you, sir?
Why didn't you add "sir?"
You smiled.
Don't you think
I'm good at making you smile?
If you don't need anything,
will you excuse me?
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you could apologize.
Tae Seok, you have changed a lot.
Tae Seok?
Tae Seok...
What did you page me for?
Have a seat first.
Sit.
Do you know Manager Kim?
The Manager Kim?
She will be reinstated
in the Housekeeping Department.
I didn't just sign it this time.
I apologized to her appropriately.
Isn't this the kind of man you like?
I can't live without you now.
Don't make me wait long, and come to me.
Come to me.
Am I bothering you?
Yes, you are.
Aren't you hungry?
Should I grab something?
Yes.
I will be right back.
Jun Seo?
Excuse me.
Who are you?
I am Yu Mi's mother.
Are you Jun Seo's cousin?
Yes.
I heard a lot about you from Yu Mi.
Do you live here?
Yes.
Ms. Eun Seo.
Do you know why Jun Seo
wants to break up with Yu Mi?
What do you mean to break up with her?
Do you know anything about it?
What have you done?
Do you know how Yu Mi is now?
What are you going to do with Yu Mi?
How could you do that,
when you knew she was in the hospital?
Is Yu Mi seriously sick?
I have nothing to say.
Are you the Jun Seo that I know?
How can you do this?
Are you seeing someone else?
- Jun Seo.
- Yes.
Did you really break up with Yu Mi?
Why? Why did you, Jun Seo?
I love someone else.
Did my mom come?
Yes.
What did she say?
Were you there?
Did you have an argument with Jun Seo?
No, it wasn't serious.
I didn't think my mom would come here.
I see.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, please help me out.
You can help me.
You are the only one who can help me.
Jun Seo cares about you a lot.
You are his sister...
he really cares about.
You are his sister, so please help me out.
I was a sickly child,
so I couldn't get along with anyone.
I was very weak, so...
I have never been helpful to Jun Seo.
I thought about leaving him several times.
But I know now.
I am nothing without Jun Seo.
Yes.
Because of his responsibility,
he has been with me. I know that.
Although I know that I...
I want him to be with me.
I want him.
I am sorry.
I am sorry, Eun Seo.
Don't say that.
But, if you stay with Jun Seo,
Mom will see you again.
I'm scared that she will get sick again.
I can't live without you now.
Don't make me wait long, and come to me.
Come to me.
I thought about leaving him several times.
But I know now.
I am nothing without Jun Seo.
Choi Eun Seo.
What are you doing?
I have no sense of shame.
So, I don't care about others
and get whatever I want.
Also, I get anything I would hate
on someone else.
Let me get you, too.
You can trust me.